A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Countries, Series E FA341
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Brazil
  - Brazil - Magalhaes, Juracy, 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 130)
    Ambassador to United States and Foreign Minister. Correspondence re: dinner at Brazilian embassy, arrangements to see Magalhaes, and to set up reception for visiting Brazilian officials.
  - Brazil - Martins, Carlos and Maria, 1943-1966 (Box 17, Folder 131)
    Carlos was Brazil's ambassador to the United States, later went into business. Maria is an art collector and sculptor. Correspondence re: United States-Latin American cooperation and private business and art matters; personal correspondence.
  - Brazil - Matarazzo, Sobrinho, Francisco, Mr. - and Mrs. Yolanda Penteado, 1950-1970 (Box 17, Folder 132)
    Francisco involved with art and the Museum of Modern Art, Sao Paulo. Yolanda also interested in art and briefly in children's hospital care. Correspondence re: art and art shows and introducing artists to NAR. Art catalogues.
  - Brazil - Moreira Salles, Walther, 1933-1970 (Box 17, Folder 133)
    Leading Brazilian businessman, finance minister of Brazil, and Brazilian ambassador to the United States. Friend of NAR. Correspondence and memos on Brazilian politics on Moreira Salles' support for IBEC (International Basic Economy Corporation); soccer appeal to NAR (referred to Moreira Salles); trip by DR and NAR to Brazil; NAR purchase of art from Moreira Salles. Banco Moreira Salles annual reports of 1957 and 1966. Copies of Ambassador's speeches.
  - Brazil - Nabuco, Jose, Dr., 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 134)
    Friend of NAR. Assorted correspondence re: Museum of Modern Art, possible exhibits of Portinari works. NAR's congratulations on son's and brother's appointments to new jobs; telegrapms re: Nabuco illness; Nabuco condolences on death of Abby Aldrich Rockefeller.
  - Brazil - Nabuco, Mauiciao, Dr., 1951-1959 (Box 17, Folder 135)
    Brazilian ambassador to the United States and President of the Museum of Modern Art, Rio. Nabuco congratulations on NAR election as Governor, clippings on various events.
  - Brazil - Nobre, Fernando de A., 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 136)
    Brazilian scholar. Introduced to NAR by Assis Chateaubriand. NAR, through Berent Friele, tried to help find a publisher for Nobre's book, introduced him to President of Columbia University. Correspondence with Immigration re: Nobre's whereabouts.
  - Brazil - Oliveira, Paulo de, 1944-1959 (Box 17, Folder 137)
    Correspondence in which Oliveira repeatedly seeks help in getting a job. Some appointments set up at United Nations, Rockefeller Foundation.
  - Brazil - Palmgen, Stig G., 1950-1952 (Box 17, Folder 138)
    International Basic Economy Corporation employee. Sent photos of NAR Brazil trip.
  - Brazil - Peixoto, de Amaral, 1945-1959 (Box 17, Folder 139)
    Governor of State of Rio de Janeiro, later Minister of Transportation and Public Works, Ambassador to United States. Clippings and correspondence re: visit of Governor Peixoto to United States as emissary of President Vargas. Seeks help from NAR in business matters with Westinghouse and in project to act as agent for Rockefeller project in South America. Personal correspondence between Peixoto and NAR re: electoral victories, marriage of NAR's son.
  - Brazil - Penna, Herculana, 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 140)
    Young man who, with a companion, Carlos Barbarosa, served as intern at the King Ranch to learn about cattle raising. Planned to help family start cattle business in Texas. NAR office assisted in placing them at the ranch.
  - Brazil - Pereira, Armanda de, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 141)
    Mayor of Sao Paulo City. Correspondence re: visit of American engineers to Sao Paulo and re: Pereira visit to United States. Attempts to set up appointment for Pereira to see President Truman at the White House. Photos of NAR visit to Sao Paulo.
  - Brazil - Pinto Alves, Carlos, Mme., 1947-1969 (Box 17, Folder 142)
    Sent birthday wishes, congratulations on election, brochure of her sculpture exhibit, article about her to NAR. All acknowledged.
  - Brazil - Quadros, Janio, 1955-1962 (Box 17, Folder 143)
    Governor of Sao Paulo, President of Brazil; resigned presidency after 8 months. Memoranda re: President-elect Quadros's likely policies, and political situation in Brazil after Quadros's resignation. Memos and telegrams re: Governor Quadros's policies, visit to United States, luncheon given by NAR.
  - Brazil - Rossi, Paulo C. - Rossi Tiles, 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 144)
    NAR office unsuccessfully tried to help import and sell in the United States tiles made by Rossi.
  - Brazil - Sanchez, Braulio, Professor, 1945-1962 (Box 18, Folder 145)
    Appeals to NAR.
  - Brazil - Samanho, Walder Lima, 1945-1948 (Box 18, Folder 145A)
    Consul General in New York. From Brazil. General correspondence re: NAR trip to Brazil, Samanho reassignment from United States.
  - Brazil - Schools (A-I), 1948-1971 (Box 18, Folder 145B)
  - Brazil - Schools (J-Z), 1948-1971 (Box 18, Folder 145C)
  - Brazil - Schools - Escola Fluminese de Medicina Veterinaria - Rio de Janeiro, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 145D)
    NAR named patron by graduating class and sent Richard Aldrich as his representative. Embarrassing situation and adverse publicity resulted. Correspondence and telegrams among NAR office, Brazil's ambassador in United States, Brazilian friends of NAR, and the school.
  - Brazil - UNIAO Cultural Brazil - Estados Unidos, 1948-1963 (Box 18, Folder 145E)
    Mailings and personal appeals to NAR. NAR interested but unable to assist. Appeal to Rockefeller Brothers Fund encouraged by Berent Friele.
  - Brazil - Vargas, Darcy Sarmanho, Fundacao Darcy Vargas, 1949-1957 (Box 18, Folder 145F)
    Appeals on behalf of New Boys' Home. NAR sent polio vaccine for 500 inoculations.
  - Brazil - President Vargas, Getulio, 1942-1953 (Box 18, Folder 145G)
    President of Brazil. Deposed one and re-elected. Some personal correspondence between NAR and Vargas. Clippings. Reports and memos to NAR re: Brazilian government policy toward United States and foreign investments and re: general political situation.
  - Brazil - Vargas, Luthero, 1942-1946 (Box 18, Folder 145H)
    File deals with Mme. Luthero Vargas, daughter-in-law of Brazilian president. She was suspected of being a Nazi spy, acting in the United States, and was watched by the F.B.I. Correspondence among J. Edgar Hoover, NAR, Mme. Martins, wife of Brazilian ambassador to the United States.
  - Brazil - Velloso, Leao, 1945-1946 (Box 19, Folder 146)
    Brazilian representative to United Nations Security Council. Died in New York. Personal correspondence.
  - Brazil - Vidigal, Gastao, 1947-1971 (Box 19, Folder 146A)
    General personal correspondence. NAR introduces Vidigal to John McCloy.
  - Brazil - Winans, Hubert C., 1948-1956 (Box 19, Folder 146B)
    Varied correspondence among NAR, Winans, and Arthur Flemming re: Brazilian restrictions on Otis Elevator Co. and on exploiting Brazilian iron ore.
- Bulgaria
  Bulgaria
  - Bulgaria - Appeals, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 147)
- Cambodia
  Cambodia
  - Cambodia - General, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 148)
- Canada
  Canada
  - Canada - General (A-C), 1947-1971 (Box 19, Folder 149)
  - Canada - General (D-G), 1947-1971 (Box 19, Folder 150)
  - Canada - General (H-L), 1947-1971 (Box 19, Folder 151)
  - Canada - General (M-Z), 1947-1971 (Box 19, Folder 152)
  - Canada - Churches, 1957-1971 (Box 19, Folder 153)
  - Canada - Schools and Colleges, 1951-1967 (Box 19, Folder 154)
    Appeals; NAR contribution to Canadian Educational Foundation.
- Ceylon
  Sri Lanka
  - Ceylon - General - Appeals, 1957-1970 (Box 19, Folder 155)
- Chile
  Chile
  - Chile - General (A-H), 1946-1970 (Box 20, Folder 156)
  - Chile - General (I-M), 1946-1970 (Box 20, Folder 157)
  - Chile - General (N-Z), 1946-1970 (Box 20, Folder 158)
  - Chile - Government, 1947-1970 (Box 20, Folder 159)
    General folder, including invitation to University of Dayton seminar, with ex-President Frei, copies of speeches by President Frei and by Foreign Minister, clippings, office memo on reorganizing Chile's debts, statement by NAR on cancellation of 1969 visit by Presidential study mission.
  - Chile - Aldunate Phillips, Raul, 1945-1970 (Box 20, Folder 160)
    Sent NAR a copy of his book on United Nations San Francisco Conference, asked NAR for assistance in business; NAR sent medicine for Phillips' father. Correspondence, clippings, memos.
  - Chile - Allesandri, Eduard, Dr., 1965-1970 (Box 20, Folder 161)
    Brother of former President of Chile, prominent in sulphur business. Correspondence and copies of proposals re: asking NAR for financial assistance for business project, asking NAR to help him procure a business loan for farm improvements, introducing General Tassara of Chile.
  - Chile - Cruz-Coke, Eduardo, 1958-1966 (Box 20, Folder 162)
    Correspondence requesting NAR assistance for friends, offering information on a new vitamin to help President Eisenhower's illness.
  - Chile - Earthquakes - Relief, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 163)
    Correspondence and accompanying press clips from Dr. Marcial Mora Miranda, President of Chilean Senate, to NAR asking NAR's personal aid in wake of earthquakes. NAR declines, points to United States Government program.
  - Chile - Espinosa Mujica, Arturo, 1943-1958 (Box 21, Folder 164)
    Wartime letter to NAR discusing South American politics, requesting more arms from Stimson for Chile; post-war correspondence includes greetings and appeals for NAR assistance in business undertakings with Du Pont and in steel.
  - Chile - Escobar, Adrian C., Dr., 1952-1953 (Box 21, Folder 165)
    Argentine ambassador, 1943, 1944, thought possibly to be pro-Nazi. Sends greetings to NAR and clippings and writes of Latin American politics and need for United States support of Latin America.
  - Chile - Fernandez Rodriguez, Lorenzo, Dr., 1952-1957 (Box 21, Folder 166)
    Appeals, sent NAR copy of his book.
  - Chile - Galdames, Adrian D., 1947 (Box 21, Folder 167)
    Developed system for teaching reading and writing and wanted to work with NAR on an education project. Correspondence and sample readers.
  - Chile - Gonzales, Videla, Gabriel and Visit to United States, April 1950 (Box 21, Folder 168)
    Former President of Chile. Memos and correspondence re: his visit to United States. NAR gave luncheon, received copy of book from IBM on visit. Letter to NAR asking NAR to support anti-Communists in 1964 election. NAR declined.
  - Chile - Mora, Marcial, M., 1945-1953 (Box 21, Folder 169)
    Chilean Ambassador to the United States, 1945-1946. Requests NAR's help in getting Ford distributorship in Chile for friends. Solicits article from NAR for Chilean Gazette. Sends good wishes, thanks NAR for Steuben glass gifts, asks help for getting job for son-in-law.
  - Chile - Rios, Juan Antonio, 1942-1946 (Box 21, Folder 170)
    President of Chile, 1942-1946. Correspondence among Rios, NAR's coordinator's office and United States Ambassador to Chile re: United States visit of President Rios, 1945. Telegram and clipping re: President Rio's death, 1946.
  - Chile - Schools and Colleges, 1950-1956 (Box 21, Folder 171)
    Appeals and requests to speak. Declined or referred elsewhere.
- China
  China
  - China - General (A-Z), 1948-1969 (Box 22, Folder 172)
    Appeals; NAR thanks Chiang for Chinese government honor, request for NAR financial aid for a Chinese secret society, copy of speech on China by Algernon Blach.
  - China - University of China, National Library of Peiping, Government - Republic of China, 1933-1971 (Box 22, Folder 173)
    Appeal by Charles Rankin, President of University to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and NAR for support. Letters discussing Rankin's views of Chinese politics. Correspondence between Mr. T. L. Yuan, director, and NAR re: possible John D. Rockefeller, Jr. support for library; declined. NAR thanks to General Yu for Chinese government honor. Copy of Asian edition, "Reader's Digest" sent.
- Colombia
  Colombia
  - Colombia - General Correspondence, 1947-1970 (Box 22, Folder 174)
    Correspondence re: private investments in Colombia, information on Colombian agriculture, and teaching English in Colombia.
  - Colombia - General (A-C), 1948-1971 (Box 22, Folder 175)
  - Colombia - General (D-G), 1948-1971 (Box 22, Folder 176)
  - Colombia - General (H-L), 1948-1971 (Box 23, Folder 177)
  - Colombia - General (M-O), 1948-1971 (Box 23, Folder 178)
  - Colombia - General (P-R), 1948-1971 (Box 23, Folder 179)
  - Colombia - General (S-Z), 1948-1971 (Box 23, Folder 180)
  - Colombia - Colleges, Bogota, University Los Andes, 1951-1970 (Box 23, Folder 181)
    Appeals declined. Extensive correspondence between University of Andes, especially Alberto Lleras Camargo, and NAR and his office. NAR supported University of Andes with contributions and helped the University obtain other support.
  - Colombia - Churches, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 182)
    Appeals, declined.
  - Colombia - Government, 1948-1970 (Box 24, Folder 183)
    Correspondence re: Carlos Lleras Restrepo, President of Colombia. NAR endorsed him for honorary degree, congratulated him on election as President. Memo re: Lleras's visit to United States; memo on interview with United States agricultural attache in Colombia who wanted to know about International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) work in Venezuela and Brazil.
  - Colombia - Gutierrez, Santiago - American Federation Movement, 1950-1951 (Box 24, Folder 184)
    Gutierrez was Secretary General of the American Federation Movement. They sent NAR material on American Federation Movement program and requested his reaction and possible support. NAR felt the aims of American Federation Movement should, if possible, be fulfilled by the United Nations.
  - Colombia - Hospitals - General, 1948-1966 (Box 24, Folder 185)
    Appeals, all declined.
  - Colombia - Children's Hospital, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 186)
    NAR interest in contributing to a children's hospital in Bogota. NAR correspondence re: hospital with President Santos of Colombia. Work of hospital stopped in Colombia, fund drive in United States failed.
  - Colombia - Junta de Accion Communal, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 187)
    Nonprofit group that helps needy families sent appeals. All declined.
  - Colombia - Lleras Camargo, Alberto, President, 1945-1969 (Box 24, Folder 188)
    Former President of Colombia, 1946-1947, 1958-1962. Former Secretary General, Organization of American States (OAS); former Director General, Pan American Union. Personal correspondence, correspondence re: International Basic Economy Corporation (President not informed on), Brazilian-Colombian relations; Lleras letter to NAR re: his work as rector of private university; resignation from the Pan American Union (copy of speech), correspondence re: Inter-American Cooperation; correspondence re: Lleras work on magazine "Semana." Clippings re: Lleras career.
  - Colombia - Relief, Bogota, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 189)
    Correspondence re: relief effort by Council of Inter-American Cooperation. NAR, Chairman of Board of Trustees, contributed $5,000.
  - Colombia - Santos, Eduardo, 1943-1969 (Box 24, Folder 190)
    Former President of Colombia elected 1946. Correspondence re: John Davison Rockefeller, Jr. meeting Santos. Correspondence with NAR as Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs on Colombian policy at Chapultepec Conference, 1945, re: guaranteeing borders of South American nations. Letter to NAR from Santos re: South American international politics, dangers of Peronism. NAR correspondence with President Santos of Colombia on Rockefeller projects being set up in Brazil and Venezuela; NAR hopes for greater consultation among nations of the Americas; President Santos letter telling of revealing talks with Franklin Delano Roosevelt on security of South America. Personal correspondence, clipping of 1950. Letter to editor of "New York Times."
  - Colombia - Schools and Colleges, 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 191)
  - Colombia - Sours, Edwin W., 1945-1947 (Box 24, Folder 192)
    Businessman. Asks NAR assistance for a friend.
  - Colombia - Zueleta Angel, Eduardo, 1946-1961 (Box 24, Folder 193)
    Chairman, Council of Organization of American States, conservative jurist and internationalist. Clippings, correspondence re: possible helicopter service in Colombia and possible Laurance Spelman Rockefeller interest in such a project. Excerpts from 1948 interview in which Zuleta notes decline of United States interest in Latin America. Zuleta comments on International Basic Economy Corporation. Zuleta report on difficulty Latin Americans had in working with United States at UNO conference in 1946.
- Costa Rica
  Costa Rica
  - Costa Rica - General (A-G), 1945-1971 (Box 25, Folder 194)
    Appeals. Also memo from anti-Communist group on 1962 elections; 1955 note from Adolph Berle re: Nicaragua-Costa Rica dispute, discussing Organization of American States' role and need for cautious United States policy toward friendship with Nicaraguan dictator Samoza.
  - Costa Rica - General (H-Z), 1945-1971 (Box 25, Folder 195)
  - Costa Rica - Cuartel Buena Vista - National Museum, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 196)
    Correspondence re: NAR donation to museum of Museum of Modern Art reproductions.
  - Costa Rica - Figueres, Jose, Dr. and Mrs., President; May 8, 1970, 1951-1970 (Box 25, Folder 197)
    Personal correspondence, copies of speech, article by Figueres, and copy of letter by President Figueres to Senator Smathers, saying that Latin America needs loans, not gifts, for development.
  - Costa Rica - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Science, 1947-1970 (Box 25, Folder 198)
    Correspondence memo re: American International Association backing for experimental farm project run by Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences of the Organization of American States. NAR's reactions and questions and suggested conditions for giving money to project. Printed material on agricultural programs.
  - Costa Rica - Law, Howard E. - Program Interamericano para la Juventud Rural (PIJR - Inter-American Rural Youth Program) Advisor, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 199)
    Law, Director of Inter-American Program for Rural Youth, founded 1960; associated with 4-H Clubs.
  - Costa Rica - Lines, Jorge A., 1945-1949 (Box 25, Folder 200)
    Offers art items (pendants, etc.) for sale. Correspondence re: package NAR did not accept.
  - Costa Rica - Schools and Colleges, 1946-1971 (Box 25, Folder 201)
  - Costa Rica - Soto-Harrison, Fernando, 1944-1969 (Box 25, Folder 202)
    Memos and correspondence to NAR re: price of Costa Rican coffee and need to keep it stable, and copy of Soto book on his role at United Nations London Conference. Correspondence as Secretary to Government with NAR as Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs.
  - Costa Rica - Van Maltzan, E. R., Dr. - Proposed Dental Clinic, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 203)
    Dr. Van Maltzan, of National Institutes of Health (United States) proposed dental clinic for Costa Rica, asked NAR support. Declined.
- Cuba
  Cuba
  - Cuba - General Correspondence, 1959-1970 (Box 26, Folder 204)
    Clippings of articles, "New York Times" ad, 1961 and memo discussing it re: lives of political prisoners, anti-Castro printed material sent to NAR.
  - Cuba - General (A-E), 1947-1969 (Box 26, Folder 205)
    Appeals. Declined.
  - Cuba - General (F-Z), 1947-1969 (Box 26, Folder 206)
  - Cuba - Churches, 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 207)
  - Cuba - Inter-American Academy of Comparative and International Law, 1945-1948 (Box 26, Folder 208)
    Printed material sent to NAR.
  - Cuba - Ponce de Leon, Raul, 1947-1948 (Box 26, Folder 209)
    Publisher, "Cuba Moderna" Magazine. Requests material from NAR; requests declined. Sends copy of magazine.
  - Cuba - Schools and Colleges, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 210)
- Czechoslovakia
  Czech Republic; Slovakia
  - Czechoslovakia - General, 1948-1971 (Box 26, Folder 211)
- Denmark
  Denmark
  - Denmark - General, 1946-1971 (Box 26, Folder 212)
  - Denmark - Schools, 1947-1959 (Box 26, Folder 213)
- Dominican Republic
  Dominican Republic
  - Dominican Republic - General Correspondence (A-L), 1947-1971 (Box 27, Folder 214)
  - Dominican Republic - General Correspondence (M-Z), 1947-1971 (Box 27, Folder 215)
  - Dominican Republic - Hospitals, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 216)
- Ecuador
  Ecuador
  - Ecuador - General Correspondence, 1948-1956 (Box 27, Folder 217)
    Clippings re: Ecuadoran government and politics; Ecuadoran American Association Newsletter re: Major 1950 developments.
  - Ecuador - General (A-D), 1947-1971 (Box 27, Folder 218)
  - Ecuador - General (E-M), 1947-1971 (Box 28, Folder 219)
  - Ecuador - General (N-R), 1947-1971 (Box 28, Folder 220)
  - Ecuador - General (S-Z), 1947-1971 (Box 28, Folder 221)
  - Ecuador - Churches, 1948-1971 (Box 28, Folder 222)
  - Ecuador - Garcia Inerarity, Jose, 1944-1971 (Box 28, Folder 223)
    Appeals. Declined. Long correspondence. Has sent gifts, praised NAR politics.
  - Ecuador - Government, 1962-1969 (Box 28, Folder 224)
    Memo re: NAR meeting, 1969, with finance minister who sought MAR in securing loan from United States for Ecuador. Memos on 1967 Presidential election. Personal correspondence.
  - Ecuador - Hospitals, 1951-1960 (Box 28, Folder 225)
  - Ecuador - Losado Carbo, Vincente, 1952-1954 (Box 28, Folder 226)
    Appeals for help in starting Latin American-United States cultural and exchange programs. Declined.
  - Ecuador - Moscoso-Cardenas, Alfonso, Dr., 1952 (Box 28, Folder 227)
    Requests to NAR on behalf of Moscoso-Cardenas, who lost his diplomatic job as a result of a change in government, for a job.
  - Ecuador - Plaza, Galo, 1948-1971 (Box 29, Folder 228)
    President of Ecuador, 1948-1952; Secretary General of Organization of American States, 1968. Ambassador to United States, 1947, 1967 letter to NAR on economic austerity program of interim government. 1961 letter to NAR critical of John F. Kennedy's handling of Cuban missile crisis, 1958 letter to NAR regretting that Latin America only received publicity in United States when the United States vice president gets a "kicking around." Copy of speech by Plaza on election eve, 1952. 1952 letter expressing preference for Eisenhower over Stevenson. Correspondence with NAR when Plaza was President re: agricultural development, Point IV program. Copies of Ambassador Plaza speeches, resignation as Ambassador in protest against Ibarr government; personal correspondence with NAR. President Galo Plaza 1949, 1951. Correspondence with NAR and NAR office re: lack of sufficient work in Ecuador for EASM, Ecuador's obtaining loans from the World Bank.
  - Ecuador - Plaza, Galo - Visit to United States, June 1951, 1951-1952 (Box 29, Folder 229)
    Correspondence re: arrangements for dinners, visit to New York City. NAR thanks for book about the visit; copies of speeches by Plaza, press releases, press clippings. Photos.
  - Ecuador - Schools, 1951-1971 (Box 29, Folder 230)
  - Ecuador - Schools, John D. Rockefeller School - Guayaquil, 1961-1964 (Box 29, Folder 231)
    NAR, at request of American Government wives, contributed. Correspondence, clippings, photos.
  - Ecuador - Guayaquil - Sociedan Union Obrera Liberal Radical Del Guayas, 1945-1949 (Box 29, Folder 232)
    Appeals. Declined. Proffered "Bolivar Decoration," NAR declined.
- Egypt
  Egypt
  - Egypt - General, 1958-1969 (Box 29, Folder 233)
  - Egypt - Aswan Dam - Art, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 234)
    Letter from May Craig, newswoman, proposing saving of monuments that would be flooded by the dam. NAR correspondence with Laurance Spelman Rockefeller on the matter. No decision.
  - Egypt - Tsirimonis, Constantin, 1958-1961 (Box 29, Folder 235)
    Appeal. Sent NAR stamps. Copy of letter of thanks.
- El Salvador
  El Salvador